Deivy Cabrera

deivy70@gmail.com / 818-334-7397 / 6936 Agnes Ave #3, North Hollywood, CA

Summary

Tech Support Specialis

Technical Support Specialist with +9 years of experience in minimizing customers downtime through prompt evaluation, troubleshooting, and repair service while keeping up with latest IT trends, techniques, and practices. Skilled in resolving software glitches, fixing system errors, and repairing hardware malfunctions.

Experience

Sales/ Tech Support for Surveillance Products and Services

CCTV.NET • Van Nuys, CA 08/2015 - 09/2021

- Meet with customers ranging from small business owners, large corporations, and government agencies to discuss their requirements to provide a network topology, equipment, and basic training for deployment.
- Manage leads, answer any presale question, invoice order using CRM software.
- Interview potential new employees to grow support team.
- Research and stay up to date with new equipment and services in order to provide a wide range of options.
- Design, Build, Maintain, and Troubleshoot surveillance servers.
- Troubleshoot and diagnose different types of equipment and provide a fast resolution. (PC's, PoE Managed switches, IP cameras, Access Control, Thermal, Lidar, DVR's, NVR's, VMS's, ect...)

Quality Assurance Technician

Kavka Corp. • Van Nuys, CA 06/2015 - 10/2015

- Test for software bugs in IOS ver. 4.2.1 To 9.1 and Android ver. 2.3 to 5.0.
- Look for damages in physical hardware, including but not limited to scratches, printing errors, faulty hardware (i.e. screen, buttons, input ports).
- Accurately log all detailed information on any unusual bugs or hardware malfunctions.
- Adhere to all safety practices

Information Technology Manager

Medical Revitalization • Pacoima, CA 09/2014 - 03/2015

- Redesign, maintain, and update company website (medicalry.com)
- Reply to email leads and answer presales questions through CRM.
- Build and deploy marketing campaigns from design to target feature selection.
- Diagnose, repair, and upgrade office computers. Design from the ground up a new networking topology for their office.
- RnD: 3D printing small basic joint for equipment repair.

Information Technology Manager

ABC Learn Inc. • Pacoima, CA 10/2012 - 02/2014

• Maintain and upgrade school wide networks for both faculty and students.

- Diagnose and repair school servers, faculty computers (Windows, Mac's), and school's student laptops (Windows, Chromebooks)
- Guide and train and update school administration when replacing or upgrading an integral part if the network in order to reduce downtime.

Sales Representative

Burbank Party Rental Inc. • Burbank, California 04/2010 - 09/2012

- Receive incoming and outgoing product orders.
- Met with clients on a daily basis to discuss and guide in planning future events.
- Managed inventory both physically and in quickbooks.
- Prepared customized client presentations and quotes
- Develop and sustain relationships with existing customer base, building rapport as a personable and trusted representative

Skills

- Customer service
- · Microsoft office
- HTML
- Linux

- Help desk
- Tech support
- Windows

- · Desktop support
- Python
- Mac OS

Education

North Hollywood High School • North Hollywood, CA 07/2009

Languages

· Spanish

· English